Look, this isn't about earning interest.
It's not about optimizing your returns.
It's about breaking
I have a feeling this
is maybe a clip from a longer form piece
of content.
But what you've got to understand
is the first three seconds we
are looking to
establish what this is about. Really,
in the first five to 10 seconds, I want to
decide whether or not I'm going to watch
this.
Look, this isn't about earning interest.
I don't know what it's about.
Now, if this was its very own clip,
like I say here,
full video now out on YouTube.
Credit card debt finance. Again,
I don't know how many more times you say
this.
The CEO of Instagram said
that hashtags don't do anything,
so stop putting them in
your bio.
It's about breaking that really horrible
cycle of paying off debt
Okay, I still don't know what this
is about.
An issue here is,
I get it because I am guilty of this
myself, where I clip up long
form content, stick it on Instagram,
and maybe I don't care that much.
However,
the beginning of this just doesn't
establish what's happening.
Now,
you've gone to the attempt here of running
an A camera and a B camera, which
means I've got a camera there
and it's like having another camera here.
I haven't even gone to
that effort for this video.
If you care that much about being able to
clip your long form
content into short form,
you should script it and structure it
that way that
you put 10 short form videos back to back.
And in essence, when you do your video,
ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, bum, you
can then just clip it into those short
form pieces of content.
And the issue is because you haven't done
that, this just doesn't really make
sense. And the way that you said,
"Right," makes me think it's not scripted
and
it's free board.
And like you can see in my last video,
I'm all about that.
I just don't feel like this
is a very strong reel